<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sleep on Fibro Hell</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/sleep/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sleep on Fibro Hell</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>License: &lt;a href=&#34;http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/4.0/&#34;&gt;CC-BY-SA-4.0&lt;/a&gt; · Author: &lt;a href=&#34;https://blog.brunomiguel.net&#34;&gt;Bruno&lt;/a&gt; · &lt;a href=&#34;https://pixabay.com/pt/vectors/voo-doo-boneca-alfinetes-vodu-5403291/&#34;&gt;Logo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&#39;m on the &lt;a rel=&#34;me&#34; href=&#34;https://masto.pt/@brunomiguel&#34;&gt;Fediverse&lt;/a&gt;
</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 00:54:45 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/sleep/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Messed up sleep continues</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/messed-up-sleep-continues/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2022 18:15:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/messed-up-sleep-continues/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I thought my sleep issues mainly had stabilized for a few months now. I have, on average, two nights without sleep, but that&amp;rsquo;s it. Long gone are the days when I slept, at most, twelve hours in a whole week. Or so I thought&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The last two weeks have been&amp;hellip; hum&amp;hellip; demanding in that regard. When I sleep, it&amp;rsquo;s usually six hours top, with one sleeping between ten and twelve because the fatigue builds up and eventually gets too much to bear. The sleepless nights have been three a week. And the sleep quality hasn&amp;rsquo;t been that great, either.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another sleepless night</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/pain-insomnia-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 04:40:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/pain-insomnia-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Again, another night awake with terrible back pain. I have a few of these, but I don&amp;rsquo;t write about them every time they happen: I save this for the worst ones. If I did, I would probably write about this once a week on average.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My legs feel numb and painful too, but not as much as my back. I should probably get a hot water bottle, but I&amp;rsquo;m a bit afraid to walk due to the numbness and pain of the legs. Shit&amp;rsquo;s bad.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A week of waking up around 8h like a fucking clock</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/fucking-clock-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Nov 2021 12:20:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/fucking-clock-1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Today was a good day. I was able to sleep around 4h and woke up at 10h and a couple of minutes, although I would&amp;rsquo;ve loved to sleep 2 or 3 more hours. The downside is that my back hurts more than usual.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Sleeping 6 hours, give or take a couple of minutes, is an improvement compared to the rest of the week, where I always woke up at 8h, 8h30, even if I fell asleep at 5h.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another sleepless night</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/pain-insomnia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Oct 2021 08:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/pain-insomnia/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This night was another sleepless one. Too much pain, even with hot water bottles. With luck, I&amp;rsquo;ll be able to fall asleep for a few hours during the morning or the afternoon. Fingers crossed (not really because they hurt).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sleep and fibromyalgia</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/sleep-and-fibro/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/sleep-and-fibro/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I’m no stranger to sleepless nights. I suffer from IBS and, on a bad flare, I would go one or two nights without sleeping. This went on and off for a few years until I could finally control this syndrome and get back to my average 9 hours of sleep.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For a few years after getting the IBS under control, I had no trouble sleeping, even when I got the flu. And then came fibromyalgia.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
