<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pain on Fibro Hell</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/pain/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pain on Fibro Hell</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>License: &lt;a href=&#34;http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/4.0/&#34;&gt;CC-BY-SA-4.0&lt;/a&gt; · Author: &lt;a href=&#34;https://blog.brunomiguel.net&#34;&gt;Bruno&lt;/a&gt; · &lt;a href=&#34;https://pixabay.com/pt/vectors/voo-doo-boneca-alfinetes-vodu-5403291/&#34;&gt;Logo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&#39;m on the &lt;a rel=&#34;me&#34; href=&#34;https://masto.pt/@brunomiguel&#34;&gt;Fediverse&lt;/a&gt;
</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 00:54:45 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/pain/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Vacations and the toll on the body</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/vacations/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2022 00:01:10 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/vacations/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The wife is on vacation this week, and, since last week, she&amp;rsquo;s been trying to butter me up to go with her to the beach because she knows how painful these things can be for me, and I usually decline. We haven&amp;rsquo;t done something like this in a while, so we both wanted to do something.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;On Monday, we arrived a little before lunch so we could eat something and then chill in the sand for a while. We were fortunate enough to find a seat in a restaurant a few meters from the beach, but not so much with the waiting time. When we started eating, my lower back was hurting like crazy - I couldn&amp;rsquo;t even stop shaking my leg.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Types of pain</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/types-of-pain/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 22:20:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/types-of-pain/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Ever since my pain started, I&amp;rsquo;ve experienced what I would classify as three different types of pain: two of them are more common, and one is rare. Usually, I feel one of them with high intensity and another with low intensity; on occasion, the three simultaneously have the same intenseness or different levels.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The most common ones are:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Feeling soared, like after receiving a solid kick in the muscles or being hit with a baseball bat (or something like that);&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Like having needles piercing my muscles.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The rarer one feels like I&amp;rsquo;m having my nerves being pulled with a hook.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cannabis and pain</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/cannabis-pain/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 05:50:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/cannabis-pain/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Since the pain from fibromyalgia started, I tried a lot of stuff to ease my suffering. I took lots of different pills, did physiotherapy, tried exercising but stopped because even light exercise increased the pain, meditation, and so on. One time, by the end of November 2020, I tried CBD. It worked at the time, but I only started to feel the effects on the first days of December that year, when I returned to work. They lasted until February 2021, when the pain increased again no matter how much CBD I took.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiple regions of my body with maximum pain intensity at the same time</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/more-high-intensity-pain-spots/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 05:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/more-high-intensity-pain-spots/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;By now, I should&amp;rsquo;ve been used to how the pain changes and fluctuates. I am not. I can&amp;rsquo;t get used to having the most hurting part of my body change from one place to the other, causing mixed difficulties as it travels - usually on my upper body. And I can&amp;rsquo;t get used to the changes in intensity, always between high levels.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Since about two weeks ago, I have had one more shit to get used to: having multiple regions of my body with maximum pain intensity at the same time. Yes: not one part of the body with the highest pain level, but two or more.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To coma or not to coma</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/to-coma-or-not-to-coma/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 23:10:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/to-coma-or-not-to-coma/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I can&amp;rsquo;t say I haven&amp;rsquo;t felt desperate due to the constant, unbearable pain and the exhaustion fibromyalgia puts me through. I&amp;rsquo;ve had some days like this, and I&amp;rsquo;ve mentioned it too. I even wrote some of the blog posts here during those periods of diminished mental energy.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I can&amp;rsquo;t also say that, as someone &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.reddit.com/r/ChronicPain/comments/s4tomz/i_wish_i_was_in_a_coma/&#34;&gt;wrote on Reddit&lt;/a&gt;, I haven&amp;rsquo;t looked at coma as a way of running away from the pain and the mental fatigue. Or worst escapes, but those desperate thoughts that come forward on the worst times won&amp;rsquo;t be the subject now. Maybe for another blog post. Or not. Fuck if I know. ^^&#39;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
