<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>pain on Fibro Hell</title>
    <link>https://fibrohell.github.io/tags/pain/</link>
    <description>Recent content in pain on Fibro Hell</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>License: &lt;a href=&#34;http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/4.0/&#34;&gt;CC-BY-SA-4.0&lt;/a&gt; · Author: &lt;a href=&#34;https://blog.brunomiguel.net&#34;&gt;Bruno&lt;/a&gt; · &lt;a href=&#34;https://pixabay.com/pt/vectors/voo-doo-boneca-alfinetes-vodu-5403291/&#34;&gt;Logo&lt;/a&gt;
</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 05:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://fibrohell.github.io/tags/pain/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Multiple regions of my body with maximum pain intensity at the same time</title>
      <link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/more-high-intensity-pain-spots/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 05:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/more-high-intensity-pain-spots/</guid>
      <description>By now, I should&amp;rsquo;ve been used to how the pain changes and fluctuates. I am not. I can&amp;rsquo;t get used to having the most hurting part of my body change from one place to the other, causing mixed difficulties as it travels - usually on my upper body. And I can&amp;rsquo;t get used to the changes in intensity, always between high levels.
Since about two weeks ago, I have had one more shit to get used to: having multiple regions of my body with maximum pain intensity at the same time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To coma or not to coma</title>
      <link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/to-coma-or-not-to-coma/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 23:10:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/to-coma-or-not-to-coma/</guid>
      <description>I can&amp;rsquo;t say I haven&amp;rsquo;t felt desperate due to the constant, unbearable pain and the exhaustion fibromyalgia puts me through. I&amp;rsquo;ve had some days like this, and I&amp;rsquo;ve mentioned it too. I even wrote some of the blog posts here during those periods of diminished mental energy.
I can&amp;rsquo;t also say that, as someone wrote on Reddit, I haven&amp;rsquo;t looked at coma as a way of running away from the pain and the mental fatigue. Or worst escapes, but those desperate thoughts that come forward on the worst times won&amp;rsquo;t be the subject now.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
