<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Medical Appointment on Fibro Hell</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/medical-appointment/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Medical Appointment on Fibro Hell</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>License: &lt;a href=&#34;http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/4.0/&#34;&gt;CC-BY-SA-4.0&lt;/a&gt; · Author: &lt;a href=&#34;https://blog.brunomiguel.net&#34;&gt;Bruno&lt;/a&gt; · &lt;a href=&#34;https://pixabay.com/pt/vectors/voo-doo-boneca-alfinetes-vodu-5403291/&#34;&gt;Logo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&#39;m on the &lt;a rel=&#34;me&#34; href=&#34;https://masto.pt/@brunomiguel&#34;&gt;Fediverse&lt;/a&gt;
</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 00:54:45 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/medical-appointment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Fifth appointment - quick notes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/fifth-appointment-quick-note/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 21:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/fifth-appointment-quick-note/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I was thinking about only writing about my fifth low intensity transcranial magnetic stimulation after a few days. Still, because I didn&amp;rsquo;t feel a significant decrease in pain, I decided to write a blog post today.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The appointment was yesterday. It came after one of the worst months, just like last month. Also, I&amp;rsquo;ve felt the average pain intensity has increased. Those are two factors that should be accounted for when judging the effects of the treatment.&#xA;After the appointment, I felt a lot of relief, but less than with the previous appointments. Even the previous one made me feel less pain, and that one didn&amp;rsquo;t provide as much pain relief as the previous ones.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fourth appointment</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/fourth-appointment/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 02:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/fourth-appointment/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;On the fifth of this month, I had my fourth transcranial magnetic stimulation appointment. It was supposed to be by the end of March. Sadly, money doesn&amp;rsquo;t stretch, and I had to reschedule it, even though I sorely needed it. March was one of the worst months I had so far: I spent most of that month only sleeping every other day.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The day of the appointment came, and I was exhausted and in much pain. Fortunately, the therapy relieved that, and I left the centre feeling much better. Yet, not as good as in the other appointments. I assume this was because, as I wrote above, I was coming from one of the worst months.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I had a chronic pain appointment that made me feel even more pain</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/chronic-pain-appointment/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 11:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/chronic-pain-appointment/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Yesterday I had a chronic pain appointment. It was insanely painful! I had to wait almost an hour to see the doctor, sitting in super uncomfortable chairs, and left there with more pain than when I entered.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This fucked up my sleep completely. I spent the night awake, in a lot of pain. After returning home, I prepared five (or was it six? i lost count) hot water bottles and had to take a boiling bath. It took me more than twelve hours to start to feel some very minor relief, and that wasn&amp;rsquo;t enough to allow me to sleep, even if by morning. I&amp;rsquo;m super sleepy, but I can sleep because I&amp;rsquo;m still in too much pain.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Third appointment done</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/third-appointment/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 00:00:10 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/third-appointment/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Yesterday, the 10th, I had my third transcranial magnetic stimulation appointment. Unlike &lt;a href=&#34;https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/second-appointment/&#34;&gt;last time&lt;/a&gt;, there was no delay; I believe it was because I was the day&amp;rsquo;s first patient. I&amp;rsquo;ll probably be the first again on the next one because it&amp;rsquo;s scheduled for the same hour as yesterday. Even if I&amp;rsquo;m not the first, I&amp;rsquo;ll be one of the first, which means I probably won&amp;rsquo;t have to wait much.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Again, I felt that fantastic relaxation feeling in my body. This time, it started during the first part of the treatment, not by the end like the previous two appointments, and only increased from there. When I left the office, I was smiling. That was crazy!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transcranial magnetic stimulation medical appointment scheduled</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/transcranial-magnetic-stimulation-appointment-scheduled/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 15:20:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/transcranial-magnetic-stimulation-appointment-scheduled/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Today, I received a call from the only medical centre in Portugal dedicated to fibromyalgia. They wanted to schedule the first appointment with me.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When I called them to schedule it, they told me they were only registering contacts and that the appointments would only be from January forward. However, today, they scheduled it for next week. I&amp;rsquo;m super excited!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
