<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>irritating on Fibro Hell</title><link>https://fibrohell.github.io/tags/irritating/</link><description>Recent content in irritating on Fibro Hell</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>License: &lt;a href="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/4.0/">CC-BY-SA-4.0&lt;/a> · Author: &lt;a href="https://blog.brunomiguel.net">Bruno&lt;/a> · &lt;a href="https://pixabay.com/pt/vectors/voo-doo-boneca-alfinetes-vodu-5403291/">Logo&lt;/a></copyright><lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 20:20:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://fibrohell.github.io/tags/irritating/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Presented myself before a medical board and left the facilities feeling like shit</title><link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/medical-board-made-me-feel-like-shit/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 20:20:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/medical-board-made-me-feel-like-shit/</guid><description>Today, I presented myself before Social Security&amp;rsquo;s medical board. I waited almost an hour and didn&amp;rsquo;t wait even more because the other people there saw my suffering and were very kind and asked them to let me cut the line.
I&amp;rsquo;ll continue on paid sick leave. As I was leaving, the &amp;ldquo;doctors&amp;rdquo; in the medical board told me it was a Christmas gift. I&amp;rsquo;m not kidding. Those fuckers mocked me and my disability. I left their facilities feeling like shit.</description></item><item><title>WhY aRe YoU iN pAiN iF yOuR eXaMs ShOw NoThInG wRoNg?</title><link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/why-are-you-in-pain/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 18:22:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/why-are-you-in-pain/</guid><description>Another common complaint I see on /r/fibromyalgia and /r/chronicpain is people asking why someone is in pain if the medical exams show nothing wrong. There is also a variation of the above question: people asking why chronic pain sufferers are in pain if they don&amp;rsquo;t have anything physically wrong.
Those are also annoying. Infuriating, I might add. Again, I won&amp;rsquo;t judge the intention when people ask these questions. However, I can&amp;rsquo;t help but ponder if people think through these questions and their impact before asking them.</description></item><item><title>HaVe YoU tRiEd (insert random stuff)?</title><link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/have-you-tried/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2021 18:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/have-you-tried/</guid><description>One common complaint I see on /r/fibromyalgia and /r/chronicpain is the questions chronic pain sufferers get asked about if they tried some random stuff, sometimes followed by an &amp;ldquo;it worked for me for my random non-chronic pain. &amp;ldquo;Your all body hurts? Try Yoga&amp;rdquo;.
These questions can be more than annoying. They can be irritating. I won&amp;rsquo;t judge the intention when people ask these questions; I only wonder if they really think people living with chronic pain haven&amp;rsquo;t tried everything they could possibly imagine to relieve the pain.</description></item></channel></rss>