<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>medical board on Fibro Hell</title>
    <link>https://fibrohell.github.io/tags/medical-board/</link>
    <description>Recent content in medical board on Fibro Hell</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>License: &lt;a href=&#34;http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/4.0/&#34;&gt;CC-BY-SA-4.0&lt;/a&gt; · Author: &lt;a href=&#34;https://blog.brunomiguel.net&#34;&gt;Bruno&lt;/a&gt; · &lt;a href=&#34;https://pixabay.com/pt/vectors/voo-doo-boneca-alfinetes-vodu-5403291/&#34;&gt;Logo&lt;/a&gt;
</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 14:50:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://fibrohell.github.io/tags/medical-board/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Medical board to me: fuck you very much</title>
      <link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/medical-board-doesnt-give-a-crap/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 14:50:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/medical-board-doesnt-give-a-crap/</guid>
      <description>On the 28th, I had to present myself again before a medical board. This time, I was not insulted, screamed at or any other crazy stuff I&amp;rsquo;ve experienced with them before. However, I was told Social Security would stop paying me my sick leave very soon. They also said that I should consider disability retirement. There&amp;rsquo;s only one thing about disability retirement: I don&amp;rsquo;t want it, and Social Security doesn&amp;rsquo;t give it to people who live with fibromyalgia, no matter how much it impacts their lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My experience with Social Security&#39;s medical boards</title>
      <link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/medical-board-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 02:50:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/medical-board-1/</guid>
      <description>Next week, I&amp;rsquo;ll have to present myself before a &amp;ldquo;medical&amp;rdquo; board. This is a standard procedure from Social Security in Portugal to assess if the person has a sickness that prevents them from working. They do this every three months or so while the person is on sick leave.
I won&amp;rsquo;t go into details about the surreal situations I&amp;rsquo;ve experienced with these &amp;ldquo;medical&amp;rdquo; boards, like being shouted at by one of the supposed doctors after another one had made me a question, and I began answering it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
