<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>fibromyalgia on Fibro Hell</title><link>https://fibrohell.github.io/tags/fibromyalgia/</link><description>Recent content in fibromyalgia on Fibro Hell</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>License: &lt;a href="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/4.0/">CC-BY-SA-4.0&lt;/a> · Author: &lt;a href="https://blog.brunomiguel.net">Bruno&lt;/a> · &lt;a href="https://pixabay.com/pt/vectors/voo-doo-boneca-alfinetes-vodu-5403291/">Logo&lt;/a>&lt;br>I'm on the &lt;a rel="me" href="https://masto.pt/@brunomiguel">Fediverse&lt;/a></copyright><lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 02:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://fibrohell.github.io/tags/fibromyalgia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Third anniversary of my living hell</title><link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/fibromyalgia-third-birthday/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 02:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/fibromyalgia-third-birthday/</guid><description>The third anniversary of my living hell is just around the corner, on the 29th. I could never imagine how my life would be turned upside down and fucked up completely, to the point of being done for the day just for cooking a quick meal.
The beginning When the pain began, it made my lower back hurt like hell, and it would spread to my hips when it got worse. For more than six months, it remained like that.</description></item><item><title>I'm so sick of the bullshit around fibromyalgia</title><link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/tired-bullshit-fibromyalgia/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 19:20:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/tired-bullshit-fibromyalgia/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m so sick of the bullshit around fibromyalgia. The latest I&amp;rsquo;ve read is an article on a Portuguese news channel website about happiness as an almost miraculous cure for this syndrome. What a bunch of steaming, stinky shit! Five fucking minutes on a search engine, and the reporter would&amp;rsquo;ve found actual medical information about this. Three examples follow below:
Autoantibodies: a possible contributor to fibromyalgia New Review Highlights Autoimmune Roots of Unexplained Chronic Pain Mouse Study Reveals An Immune Cell That May Cause Fibromyalgia Shit like this creates a lot of obstacles to getting actual help.</description></item></channel></rss>