<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>sleep on Fibro Hell</title><link>https://fibrohell.github.io/tags/sleep/</link><description>Recent content in sleep on Fibro Hell</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>License: &lt;a href="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/4.0/">CC-BY-SA-4.0&lt;/a> · Author: &lt;a href="https://blog.brunomiguel.net">Bruno&lt;/a> · &lt;a href="https://pixabay.com/pt/vectors/voo-doo-boneca-alfinetes-vodu-5403291/">Logo&lt;/a></copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 04:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://fibrohell.github.io/tags/sleep/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Starting 2022 worst than I ended 2021</title><link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/starting-2022-with-left-foot/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 04:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/starting-2022-with-left-foot/</guid><description>Two days after Christmas, I wrote about how painful and tiring the holiday was for me. If you read it, you know that I didn&amp;rsquo;t have much sleep on top of what I just mentioned. I can&amp;rsquo;t say it wasn&amp;rsquo;t expected because it was.
Although a quiet one, the New Year celebration was also expected to be painful and tiring. It was. No surprise here.
After these holidays, I thought I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t get worse than I already was - a few days to recover, and that would be it.</description></item><item><title>The Hellidays were like a beaten to my body</title><link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/hellidays/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2021 04:10:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/hellidays/</guid><description>The Hellidays are gone, and my body is happy with that. Christmas Eve was on a Sunday and Christmas on a Saturday. Then came Sunday, like the third day of the Hellidays. What a fucking beaten it was for me.
On Christmas Eve, I stayed at home during the morning and almost all afternoon. Thank Zeus for that. I couldn&amp;rsquo;t sleep the previous night, only a few hours during the morning. The afternoon was to rest my body and do hot water bottles to ease the pain.</description></item><item><title>My arms hurt as much as my back</title><link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/arms-hurting-like-hell/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Dec 2021 03:30:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/arms-hurting-like-hell/</guid><description>Yesterday and, so far, today have been crazy and not in a good way. I&amp;rsquo;ve felt pain in my shoulders, arms, hands and wrists since this started, but not so much as now. The intensity is way up there!
It&amp;rsquo;s not just the pain, but the soreness and exhaustion I feel in them too. Yesterday, I even put a hot water bottle in my arms to ease the pain. I&amp;rsquo;ve never done such a thing before!</description></item><item><title>Another sleepless night</title><link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/pain-insomnia-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 04:40:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/pain-insomnia-2/</guid><description>Again, another night awake with terrible back pain. I have a few of these, but I don&amp;rsquo;t write about them every time they happen: I save this for the worst ones. If I did, I would probably write about this once a week on average.
My legs feel numb and painful too, but not as much as my back. I should probably get a hot water bottle, but I&amp;rsquo;m a bit afraid to walk due to the numbness and pain of the legs.</description></item><item><title>A week of waking up around 8h like a fucking clock</title><link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/fucking-clock-1/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Nov 2021 12:20:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/fucking-clock-1/</guid><description>Today was a good day. I was able to sleep around 4h and woke up at 10h and a couple of minutes, although I would&amp;rsquo;ve loved to sleep 2 or 3 more hours. The downside is that my back hurts more than usual.
Sleeping 6 hours, give or take a couple of minutes, is an improvement compared to the rest of the week, where I always woke up at 8h, 8h30, even if I fell asleep at 5h.</description></item><item><title>Another sleepless night</title><link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/pain-insomnia/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Oct 2021 08:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/pain-insomnia/</guid><description>This night was another sleepless one. Too much pain, even with hot water bottles. With luck, I&amp;rsquo;ll be able to fall asleep for a few hours during the morning or the afternoon. Fingers crossed (not really because they hurt).</description></item><item><title>Sleep and fibromyalgia</title><link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/sleep-and-fibro/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/sleep-and-fibro/</guid><description>I’m no stranger to sleepless nights. I suffer from IBS and, on a bad flare, I would go one or two nights without sleeping. This went on and off for a few years until I could finally control this syndrome and get back to my average 9 hours of sleep.
For a few years after getting the IBS under control, I had no trouble sleeping, even when I got the flu. And then came fibromyalgia.</description></item></channel></rss>