<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Scientific Studies on Fibro Hell</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/series/scientific-studies/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Scientific Studies on Fibro Hell</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>License: &lt;a href=&#34;http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/4.0/&#34;&gt;CC-BY-SA-4.0&lt;/a&gt; · Author: &lt;a href=&#34;https://blog.brunomiguel.net&#34;&gt;Bruno&lt;/a&gt; · &lt;a href=&#34;https://pixabay.com/pt/vectors/voo-doo-boneca-alfinetes-vodu-5403291/&#34;&gt;Logo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&#39;m on the &lt;a rel=&#34;me&#34; href=&#34;https://masto.pt/@brunomiguel&#34;&gt;Fediverse&lt;/a&gt;
</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 19:57:04 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/series/scientific-studies/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;m so sick of the bullshit around fibromyalgia</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/tired-bullshit-fibromyalgia/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 19:20:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/tired-bullshit-fibromyalgia/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m so sick of the bullshit around fibromyalgia. The latest I&amp;rsquo;ve read is an &lt;a href=&#34;https://sicnoticias.pt/saude-e-bem-estar/2023-05-12-Fibromialgia-O-medico-escreveu-felicidade-num-papel-e-deu-mo.-Foi-tudo-o-que-eu-precisei-d08b49a2&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;article&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; on a Portuguese news channel website about happiness as an almost miraculous cure for this syndrome. What a bunch of steaming, stinky shit! Five fucking minutes on a search engine, and the reporter would&amp;rsquo;ve found actual medical information about this. Three examples follow below:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://news.ki.se/autoantibodies-a-possible-contributor-to-fibromyalgia&#34;&gt;Autoantibodies: a possible contributor to fibromyalgia&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.practicalpainmanagement.com/news/new-review-highlights-autoimmune-roots-of-unexplained-chronic-pain&#34;&gt;New Review Highlights Autoimmune Roots of Unexplained Chronic Pain&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sciencealert.com/mouse-study-reveals-an-immune-cell-that-may-cause-fibromyalgia&#34;&gt;Mouse Study Reveals An Immune Cell That May Cause Fibromyalgia&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Shit like this creates a lot of obstacles to getting actual help. Instead, it helps perpetuate the habit of dosing patients with antidepressants instead of prescribing medication that actually helps deal with the pain. I&amp;rsquo;m struggling with this: my meds barely have any impact on my pain management, and I can&amp;rsquo;t get a doctor to prescribe anything stronger because&amp;hellip; happiness, antidepressants, and all that bullshit.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Study shows that Transcranial Magnetic Stimulation can help decrease the pain</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/transcranial-magnetic-stimulation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 06:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/transcranial-magnetic-stimulation/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Two weeks ago, if memory serves me right, I watched the news on TV about a centre dedicated to fibromyalgia opening here I&amp;rsquo;m Portugal. They are performing a study using repetitive transcranial magnetic stimulation (rTMS), which got my attention. I searched for publications about this treatment and got my hands on a 2010 research.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the study, the authors hypothesize, based on previous works, that dysfunctions in the central nervous system related to changes in central pain processing could be the cause.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The impact of chronic pain in memory and concentration</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/chronic-pain-memory-concentration/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 06:32:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/chronic-pain-memory-concentration/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In 2007, researchers Dr. Bruce D. Dick and Dr. Saifudin Rashiq&lt;/strong&gt;, from the University of Alberta&amp;rsquo;s Multidisciplinary Pain Centre in Edmonton, Canada, &lt;strong&gt;confirmed chronic pain impairs memory and concentration.&lt;/strong&gt; Two-thirds of the participants in the research showed significant disruption of attention and memory when tested.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Computerized tests were given to the 24 participants, all of whom had continuous pain lasting for at least six months, to understand the impact of chronic pain on memory. These tests were of working memory and a neuropsychological test of attention.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>List of recent fibromyalgia studies</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/list-of-studies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Nov 2021 03:42:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/list-of-studies/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I compiled, below, a small list of recent fibromyalgia scientific studies with open access so that people diagnosed with it can better understand the syndrome and find ways to improve symptoms management. Also, people who don&amp;rsquo;t have it can better understand how much patients diagnosed with it suffer.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;list&#34;&gt;List&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC2990568/&#34;&gt;Fibromyalgia—A Review for the Psychiatrist&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S1053811920303633?via%3Dihub&#34;&gt;Default mode network changes in fibromyalgia patients are largely dependent on current clinical pain&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.jbc.org/article/S0021-9258%2820%2940006-7/fulltext&#34;&gt;Metabolic fingerprinting for diagnosis of fibromyalgia and other rheumatologic disorders&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fibromyalgia might be an autoimmune disease</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/fibro-auto-imune-disease-study/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Nov 2021 00:48:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/fibro-auto-imune-disease-study/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A recent study points to the hypothesis that fibromyalgia might be an autoimmune disease.&lt;/strong&gt; The research is being developed by the Institute of Psychiatry, Psychology &amp;amp; Neuroscience at King’s College London, collaborating with the University of Liverpool and the Karolinska Institute.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Fibromyalgia patients suffer from several symptoms, such as pain sensitivity, muscle weakness, increased fatigue, reduced movement, and reduced number of small nerve fibres in the skin. &lt;strong&gt;The research is revealing the root of these symptoms is antibodies that increase the activity of pain-sensing nerves throughout the body.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
