<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>energy on Fibro Hell</title><link>https://fibrohell.github.io/tags/energy/</link><description>Recent content in energy on Fibro Hell</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>License: &lt;a href="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/4.0/">CC-BY-SA-4.0&lt;/a> · Author: &lt;a href="https://blog.brunomiguel.net">Bruno&lt;/a> · &lt;a href="https://pixabay.com/pt/vectors/voo-doo-boneca-alfinetes-vodu-5403291/">Logo&lt;/a></copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 17:40:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://fibrohell.github.io/tags/energy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A walk in the park</title><link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/a-walk-in-the-park/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 17:40:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/a-walk-in-the-park/</guid><description>On the 10th, the wife and I went to a park within walking distance from home to celebrate her negative Covid test. It takes less than 5 minutes to get there on foot. Still, it took us ~15 minutes because I was walking super slow and with considerable difficulties.
When we arrived, I was with one foot to the grave. I had to sit for a while (but I actually wanted to lay down on the floor), and then I proceeded to take some photos.</description></item><item><title>Another very, very bad day</title><link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/another-very-very-bad-day/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Dec 2021 13:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/another-very-very-bad-day/</guid><description>Today is one of those days I don&amp;rsquo;t even get some pain relief by lying down. Well, it started yesterday, when I woke up. I don&amp;rsquo;t know if it was for sleeping too much time in the same position, bad luck, or whatever the fuck it was, but all I know is I woke up in tremendous pain.
My body feels like it&amp;rsquo;s broken and all soared. My arms, legs, lower back, and shoulder blades all hurt a lot.</description></item><item><title>I wake up feeling like I ran a marathon</title><link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/energy-depleted/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 10:36:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/energy-depleted/</guid><description>Some of the memories I have from my childhood and teenage years have in common that I never ran out of energy, like the Duracell bunny. During summer, It was usual for my colleagues from my home town and me to play futsal for more than four straight hours. Playing a whole morning and an entire afternoon was also not uncommon, just like going to parties after the matches to get drunk and playing another futsal match the next day wasn&amp;rsquo;t too.</description></item></channel></rss>