<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Energy on Fibro Hell</title><link>https://fibrohell.github.io/tags/energy/</link><description>Recent content in Energy on Fibro Hell</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><copyright>License: &lt;a href="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/4.0/">CC-BY-SA-4.0&lt;/a> · Author: &lt;a href="https://blog.brunomiguel.net">Bruno&lt;/a> · &lt;a href="https://pixabay.com/pt/vectors/voo-doo-boneca-alfinetes-vodu-5403291/">Logo&lt;/a>&lt;br>I'm on the &lt;a rel="me" href="https://masto.pt/@brunomiguel">Fediverse&lt;/a></copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 15:56:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://fibrohell.github.io/tags/energy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The holidays</title><link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/the-holidays/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 15:50:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/the-holidays/</guid><description>&lt;p>This time of the year is extra exhausting. Meeting with the family, traveling, talking, sitting down for long periods&amp;hellip; All of this and more pushed the fatigue levels to new heights! It&amp;rsquo;s even worse with the pain level!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Ho ho&amp;hellip; Oh no, I&amp;rsquo;m beaten!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Covid, Fibromyalgia, and an increase in fatigue</title><link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/fibromyalgia-covid/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 17:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/fibromyalgia-covid/</guid><description>&lt;p>Around two weeks ago, I began to experience Covid-19 symptoms. I was afraid it would make me feel even more pain. Thank Zeus it didn&amp;rsquo;t. My average pain level decreased, but not the peak level.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The Covid-19 symptoms I experienced were a runny nose, expectoration, cough, irritated throat, and an even higher fatigue level. Almost all of them are gone, except for the more significant fatigue feeling. Most days, I feel even more tired and have a more challenging time doing anything.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>A walk in the park</title><link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/a-walk-in-the-park/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 17:40:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/a-walk-in-the-park/</guid><description>&lt;p>On the 10th, the wife and I went to a park within walking distance from home to celebrate her negative Covid test. It takes less than 5 minutes to get there on foot. Still, it took us ~15 minutes because I was walking super slow and with considerable difficulties.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>When we arrived, I was with one foot to the grave. I had to sit for a while (but I actually wanted to lay down on the floor), and then I proceeded to take some photos. I felt super happy hanging out with her in a lovely park and shooting pictures, which depleted my energy.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Another very, very bad day</title><link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/another-very-very-bad-day/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Dec 2021 13:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/another-very-very-bad-day/</guid><description>&lt;p>Today is one of those days I don&amp;rsquo;t even get some pain relief by lying down. Well, it started yesterday, when I woke up. I don&amp;rsquo;t know if it was for sleeping too much time in the same position, bad luck, or whatever the fuck it was, but all I know is I woke up in tremendous pain.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>My body feels like it&amp;rsquo;s broken and all soared. My arms, legs, lower back, and shoulder blades all hurt a lot. And I mean a lot! Writing this is painful, and I have to do it slowly, or I might scream. I can&amp;rsquo;t even think straight.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>I wake up feeling like I ran a marathon</title><link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/energy-depleted/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 10:36:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/energy-depleted/</guid><description>&lt;p>Some of the memories I have from my childhood and teenage years have in common that &lt;strong>I never ran out of energy, like the Duracell bunny&lt;/strong>. During summer, It was usual for my colleagues from my home town and me to play futsal for more than four straight hours. &lt;strong>Playing a whole morning and an entire afternoon was also not uncommon, just like going to parties after the matches to get drunk and playing another futsal match the next day wasn&amp;rsquo;t too.&lt;/strong>&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>