<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>weather on Fibro Hell</title>
    <link>https://fibrohell.github.io/tags/weather/</link>
    <description>Recent content in weather on Fibro Hell</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>License: &lt;a href=&#34;http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/4.0/&#34;&gt;CC-BY-SA-4.0&lt;/a&gt; · Author: &lt;a href=&#34;https://blog.brunomiguel.net&#34;&gt;Bruno&lt;/a&gt; · &lt;a href=&#34;https://pixabay.com/pt/vectors/voo-doo-boneca-alfinetes-vodu-5403291/&#34;&gt;Logo&lt;/a&gt;
</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 11:10:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://fibrohell.github.io/tags/weather/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How I keep an increase of pain at bay on family days</title>
      <link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/weekend-hacks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 11:10:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/weekend-hacks/</guid>
      <description>All the doctors I&amp;rsquo;ve seen have told me I need to leave the house and mingle. I hadn&amp;rsquo;t done it much because I&amp;rsquo;m always in pain, and spending a day with the family can be exhausting and painful. I took their advice and every Sunday I try to spend it with my parents or her parents.
Doing it and avoiding the crazy amount of fatigue and pain associated with these days takes some planning. I can&amp;rsquo;t spend all day standing up, but I also can&amp;rsquo;t spend it sitting down on uncomfortable chairs, or I&amp;rsquo;ll be in a lot of pain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>O Christmas tree, O Christmas tree, how painful are your cold days</title>
      <link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/winter-pain/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 23:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/winter-pain/</guid>
      <description>The days keep getting colder and colder, and bearing my pain harder and harder. I write this semi-sitting on the bed, with my back against two pillows, my fingers hurting like crazy, my body hurting even more just for existing. I fucking hate the cold weather!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I hate cold weather</title>
      <link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/i-hate-cold-weather/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Oct 2021 06:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/i-hate-cold-weather/</guid>
      <description>Cold temperatures arrived in Portugal. With them came an increase in the pain level. What was already bad just became worst.
I was never a big fan of cold, except when I could spend the day in bed, all cosied up. Since fibromyalgia came into my life, it’s different: I can’t spend a whole day laying down because it will make my body hurt even more, and the cold makes the pain even worst.
An average pain level of 6, on a 0 to 10 scale, is now a 7.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
