<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>exhaustion on Fibro Hell</title><link>https://fibrohell.github.io/tags/exhaustion/</link><description>Recent content in exhaustion on Fibro Hell</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>License: &lt;a href="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/4.0/">CC-BY-SA-4.0&lt;/a> · Author: &lt;a href="https://blog.brunomiguel.net">Bruno&lt;/a> · &lt;a href="https://pixabay.com/pt/vectors/voo-doo-boneca-alfinetes-vodu-5403291/">Logo&lt;/a>&lt;br>I'm on the &lt;a rel="me" href="https://masto.pt/@brunomiguel">Fediverse&lt;/a></copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 17:40:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://fibrohell.github.io/tags/exhaustion/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A walk in the park</title><link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/a-walk-in-the-park/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 17:40:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/a-walk-in-the-park/</guid><description>On the 10th, the wife and I went to a park within walking distance from home to celebrate her negative Covid test. It takes less than 5 minutes to get there on foot. Still, it took us ~15 minutes because I was walking super slow and with considerable difficulties.
When we arrived, I was with one foot to the grave. I had to sit for a while (but I actually wanted to lay down on the floor), and then I proceeded to take some photos.</description></item><item><title>Starting 2022 worst than I ended 2021</title><link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/starting-2022-with-left-foot/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 04:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/starting-2022-with-left-foot/</guid><description>Two days after Christmas, I wrote about how painful and tiring the holiday was for me. If you read it, you know that I didn&amp;rsquo;t have much sleep on top of what I just mentioned. I can&amp;rsquo;t say it wasn&amp;rsquo;t expected because it was.
Although a quiet one, the New Year celebration was also expected to be painful and tiring. It was. No surprise here.
After these holidays, I thought I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t get worse than I already was - a few days to recover, and that would be it.</description></item><item><title>The Hellidays were like a beaten to my body</title><link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/hellidays/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2021 04:10:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/hellidays/</guid><description>The Hellidays are gone, and my body is happy with that. Christmas Eve was on a Sunday and Christmas on a Saturday. Then came Sunday, like the third day of the Hellidays. What a fucking beaten it was for me.
On Christmas Eve, I stayed at home during the morning and almost all afternoon. Thank Zeus for that. I couldn&amp;rsquo;t sleep the previous night, only a few hours during the morning. The afternoon was to rest my body and do hot water bottles to ease the pain.</description></item><item><title>My arms hurt as much as my back</title><link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/arms-hurting-like-hell/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Dec 2021 03:30:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/arms-hurting-like-hell/</guid><description>Yesterday and, so far, today have been crazy and not in a good way. I&amp;rsquo;ve felt pain in my shoulders, arms, hands and wrists since this started, but not so much as now. The intensity is way up there!
It&amp;rsquo;s not just the pain, but the soreness and exhaustion I feel in them too. Yesterday, I even put a hot water bottle in my arms to ease the pain. I&amp;rsquo;ve never done such a thing before!</description></item><item><title>Another very, very bad day</title><link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/another-very-very-bad-day/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Dec 2021 13:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/another-very-very-bad-day/</guid><description>Today is one of those days I don&amp;rsquo;t even get some pain relief by lying down. Well, it started yesterday, when I woke up. I don&amp;rsquo;t know if it was for sleeping too much time in the same position, bad luck, or whatever the fuck it was, but all I know is I woke up in tremendous pain.
My body feels like it&amp;rsquo;s broken and all soared. My arms, legs, lower back, and shoulder blades all hurt a lot.</description></item><item><title>I wake up feeling like I ran a marathon</title><link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/energy-depleted/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 10:36:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/energy-depleted/</guid><description>Some of the memories I have from my childhood and teenage years have in common that I never ran out of energy, like the Duracell bunny. During summer, It was usual for my colleagues from my home town and me to play futsal for more than four straight hours. Playing a whole morning and an entire afternoon was also not uncommon, just like going to parties after the matches to get drunk and playing another futsal match the next day wasn&amp;rsquo;t too.</description></item></channel></rss>