<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>treatment on Fibro Hell</title><link>https://fibrohell.github.io/tags/treatment/</link><description>Recent content in treatment on Fibro Hell</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>License: &lt;a href="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/4.0/">CC-BY-SA-4.0&lt;/a> · Author: &lt;a href="https://blog.brunomiguel.net">Bruno&lt;/a> · &lt;a href="https://pixabay.com/pt/vectors/voo-doo-boneca-alfinetes-vodu-5403291/">Logo&lt;/a></copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 07:05:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://fibrohell.github.io/tags/treatment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How it felt after the third appointment</title><link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/third-appointment-report/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 07:05:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/third-appointment-report/</guid><description>Third appointment On the 10th of February, I had the third transcranial magnetic stimulation appointment. I felt a mix of excitement and expectation and a fear the relief would be shorter than it has been or never exist again. In terms of percentages, it was around 80% excitement and 20% fear. That and a total dose of lack of sleep on the previous night.
My fear was unfounded, thank Zeus! The relief started making itself feel mid-appointment.</description></item><item><title>The pain relief didn't last long</title><link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/pain-increase-back/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 01:45:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/pain-increase-back/</guid><description>I thought the effects would last longer when I published the previous blog post. I wasn&amp;rsquo;t sure about them enduring a whole week, but at least five days. Not this time; maybe next time. Even so, it lasted longer than last month, so I call it progress, and I keep myself hopeful about this treatment!
Thirty minutes, more or less, after publishing that blog post, I started feeling an increase in the pain intensity. It went from a 2.</description></item><item><title>Still feeling the treatment effects</title><link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/second-appointment-less-pain/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 01:30:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/second-appointment-less-pain/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s already past 1 AM here in Portugal. I was expecting yesterday would be a day with more pain than usual, just like last month, three days after my first transcranial magnetic stimulation appointment.
Pessimistic as it may sound, I believe it&amp;rsquo;s better, in this particular case, to be prepared for the worse in case it happens. If it doesn&amp;rsquo;t, it&amp;rsquo;s a nice and pleasant surprise, don&amp;rsquo;t you agree?
Well, the worst-case scenario didn&amp;rsquo;t come to fruition.</description></item><item><title>Second transcranial magnetic stimulation appointment</title><link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/second-appointment/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 01:20:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/second-appointment/</guid><description>Yesterday I had my second appointment for transcranial magnetic stimulation, a treatment I&amp;rsquo;m undertaking to decrease and manage my pain levels associated with the fibromyalgia I was diagnosed with.
The consultation had a two-hour delay, far from an ideal situation. It&amp;rsquo;s 200kms from my home to the medical centre, so waiting 2 hours, having arrived on time, it&amp;rsquo;s bothersome, to say the least. While I was waiting, I had to shift between sitting and standing up to minimize the increase in the pain level, but in the end, it was worth it.</description></item><item><title>The third day after the first therapy session</title><link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/third-day/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 03:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/third-day/</guid><description>Yesterday was the third day after the first transcranial neurostimulation session. On the first day, as I wrote before, a tingling sensation started right after the therapy (well, technically, it began during it), and it increased a little as time went by. In over a year, it was the first time that I felt my body relaxing, so it felt terrific.
Unfortunately, the 200km ride back home was tiring. When we got home, I had to go straight to the couch.</description></item><item><title>I had my first transcranial neurostimulation appointment</title><link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/first-transcranial-neurostimulation-appointment/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 01:50:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/first-transcranial-neurostimulation-appointment/</guid><description>Yesterday, the 13th of December, I had my first appointment for transcranial neurostimulation, a promising therapy for dealing - and hopefully fixing - fibromyalgia. I&amp;rsquo;ve written previously about this therapy here and here.
The wife and I drove 200kms to the medical centre, the only one in Portugal with a unit dedicated exclusively to this syndrome, located in Covilhã, a city in the country&amp;rsquo;s interior region. The trip was exhausting; I had to sit for 2 hours and a few minutes, and my body complained a lot.</description></item></channel></rss>