<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fibro Hell</title>
    <link>https://fibrohell.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Fibro Hell</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>License: &lt;a href=&#34;http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/4.0/&#34;&gt;CC-BY-SA-4.0&lt;/a&gt; · Author: &lt;a href=&#34;https://blog.brunomiguel.net&#34;&gt;Bruno&lt;/a&gt; · &lt;a href=&#34;https://pixabay.com/pt/vectors/voo-doo-boneca-alfinetes-vodu-5403291/&#34;&gt;Logo&lt;/a&gt;
</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 00:40:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://fibrohell.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;m terrified about my future</title>
      <link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/terrified-about-my-future/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 00:40:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/terrified-about-my-future/</guid>
      <description>On the 16th, I&amp;rsquo;ll be 39, and I&amp;rsquo;ve never been more terrified of my future in my whole life. The pain has been getting more intense in the last few months, and I fear it will worsen.
My days are spent lying down on the couch and/or on the bed, feeling pain 24/7, not resting well when I&amp;rsquo;m able to sleep, not sleeping because the pain keeps me awake, and having my brain totally fucked up and tired&amp;hellip; I&amp;rsquo;m frightened about my future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vacations and the toll on the body</title>
      <link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/vacations/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2022 00:01:10 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/vacations/</guid>
      <description>The wife is on vacation this week, and, since last week, she&amp;rsquo;s been trying to butter me up to go with her to the beach because she knows how painful these things can be for me, and I usually decline. We haven&amp;rsquo;t done something like this in a while, so we both wanted to do something.
On Monday, we arrived a little before lunch so we could eat something and then chill in the sand for a while.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Types of pain</title>
      <link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/types-of-pain/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 22:20:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/types-of-pain/</guid>
      <description>Ever since my pain started, I&amp;rsquo;ve experienced what I would classify as three different types of pain: two of them are more common, and one is rare. Usually, I feel one of them with high intensity and another with low intensity; on occasion, the three simultaneously have the same intenseness or different levels.
The most common ones are:
Feeling soared, like after receiving a solid kick in the muscles or being hit with a baseball bat (or something like that); Like having needles piercing my muscles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cannabis and pain</title>
      <link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/cannabis-pain/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 05:50:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/cannabis-pain/</guid>
      <description>Since the pain from fibromyalgia started, I tried a lot of stuff to ease my suffering. I took lots of different pills, did physiotherapy, tried exercising but stopped because even light exercise increased the pain, meditation, and so on. One time, by the end of November 2020, I tried CBD. It worked at the time, but I only started to feel the effects on the first days of December that year, when I returned to work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About the good of humankind</title>
      <link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/about-the-good-of-humankind/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 00:55:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/about-the-good-of-humankind/</guid>
      <description>A while ago, I confided with some folks that things were getting a bit hard on the money side. My sick leave is meagre at best. It&amp;rsquo;s not enough for all the medication - not just for the fibromyalgia - I take during the month and for my monthly appointment and related costs (like gas and tolls). The wife works - and a lot, on top of that. Since I was forced to go on sick leave, she&amp;rsquo;s had to support all the costs like rent, food, and utility bills&amp;hellip; You can only stretch the money so much before it rips.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Covid, Fibromyalgia, and an increase in fatigue</title>
      <link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/fibromyalgia-covid/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 17:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/fibromyalgia-covid/</guid>
      <description>Around two weeks ago, I began to experience Covid-19 symptoms. I was afraid it would make me feel even more pain. Thank Zeus it didn&amp;rsquo;t. My average pain level decreased, but not the peak level.
The Covid-19 symptoms I experienced were a runny nose, expectoration, cough, irritated throat, and an even higher fatigue level. Almost all of them are gone, except for the more significant fatigue feeling. Most days, I feel even more tired and have a more challenging time doing anything.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A walk in the park</title>
      <link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/a-walk-in-the-park/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 17:40:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/a-walk-in-the-park/</guid>
      <description>On the 10th, the wife and I went to a park within walking distance from home to celebrate her negative Covid test. It takes less than 5 minutes to get there on foot. Still, it took us ~15 minutes because I was walking super slow and with considerable difficulties.
When we arrived, I was with one foot to the grave. I had to sit for a while (but I actually wanted to lay down on the floor), and then I proceeded to take some photos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fifth appointment - quick notes</title>
      <link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/fifth-appointment-quick-note/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 21:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/fifth-appointment-quick-note/</guid>
      <description>I was thinking about only writing about my fifth low intensity transcranial magnetic stimulation after a few days. Still, because I didn&amp;rsquo;t feel a significant decrease in pain, I decided to write a blog post today.
The appointment was yesterday. It came after one of the worst months, just like last month. Also, I&amp;rsquo;ve felt the average pain intensity has increased. Those are two factors that should be accounted for when judging the effects of the treatment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fourth appointment</title>
      <link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/fourth-appointment/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 02:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/fourth-appointment/</guid>
      <description>On the fifth of this month, I had my fourth transcranial magnetic stimulation appointment. It was supposed to be by the end of March. Sadly, money doesn&amp;rsquo;t stretch, and I had to reschedule it, even though I sorely needed it. March was one of the worst months I had so far: I spent most of that month only sleeping every other day.
The day of the appointment came, and I was exhausted and in much pain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finding purpose</title>
      <link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/finding-purpose/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2022 18:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/finding-purpose/</guid>
      <description>Suffering from pain 24/7 can deprive you of a sense of purpose. Suddenly, you find yourself dependent on others; accomplishing the most basic tasks is a huge struggle; you feel useless and a hindrance to everyone around you. &amp;ldquo;Why am I so useless?&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Why me?&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;This is no way to live&amp;rdquo; will be some thoughts that will frequently go through your mind.
How can you find a sense of purpose if your body and mind take a beating from chronic pain?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I had a chronic pain appointment that made me feel even more pain</title>
      <link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/chronic-pain-appointment/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 11:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/chronic-pain-appointment/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday I had a chronic pain appointment. It was insanely painful! I had to wait almost an hour to see the doctor, sitting in super uncomfortable chairs, and left there with more pain than when I entered.
This fucked up my sleep completely. I spent the night awake, in a lot of pain. After returning home, I prepared five (or was it six? i lost count) hot water bottles and had to take a boiling bath.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Messed up sleep continues</title>
      <link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/messed-up-sleep-continues/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2022 18:15:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/messed-up-sleep-continues/</guid>
      <description>I thought my sleep issues mainly had stabilized for a few months now. I have, on average, two nights without sleep, but that&amp;rsquo;s it. Long gone are the days when I slept, at most, twelve hours in a whole week. Or so I thought&amp;hellip;
The last two weeks have been&amp;hellip; hum&amp;hellip; demanding in that regard. When I sleep, it&amp;rsquo;s usually six hours top, with one sleeping between ten and twelve because the fatigue builds up and eventually gets too much to bear.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Medical board to me: fuck you very much</title>
      <link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/medical-board-doesnt-give-a-crap/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 14:50:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/medical-board-doesnt-give-a-crap/</guid>
      <description>On the 28th, I had to present myself again before a medical board. This time, I was not insulted, screamed at or any other crazy stuff I&amp;rsquo;ve experienced with them before. However, I was told Social Security would stop paying me my sick leave very soon. They also said that I should consider disability retirement. There&amp;rsquo;s only one thing about disability retirement: I don&amp;rsquo;t want it, and Social Security doesn&amp;rsquo;t give it to people who live with fibromyalgia, no matter how much it impacts their lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>High level, non-stopping</title>
      <link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/high-level-never-ending/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2022 07:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/high-level-never-ending/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been seeing this image on some subreddits, and I can’t imagine how great it would be if my pain was a never-ending, low-level one. I swear to Cthulhu, it would be amazing! No more sleepless nights because the pain is too much to bear, so much less brain fog and fucked up memory. Granted, I do have a couple of days of relief after the appointments, but even that starts to degrade fast hours after finishing the treatment session.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How it felt after the third appointment</title>
      <link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/third-appointment-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 07:05:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/third-appointment-report/</guid>
      <description>On the 10th of February, I had the third transcranial magnetic stimulation appointment. I felt a mix of excitement and expectation and a fear the relief would be shorter than it has been or never exist again. In terms of percentages, it was around 80% excitement and 20% fear. That and a total dose of lack of sleep on the previous night.
My fear was unfounded, thank Zeus! The relief started making itself feel mid-appointment. During that day, it only decreased during the two-hour ride home, which was expected.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tracking the therapy progress</title>
      <link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/tracking-therapy-progress/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 02:50:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/tracking-therapy-progress/</guid>
      <description>Ever since I started transcranial magnetic stimulation therapy, I&amp;rsquo;ve wanted an easy way for me to keep track of its effects. I carried out trials with a few methods, but they all fell short.
First, I experimented with writing text/markdown/org files, but it got messier as the notes grew. Then, dedicated simple note-taking software like Google Keep, but this method had the same issues as the text files. I needed context, relationships and simple search, and none of the methods above had all of these prerequisites.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Third appointment done</title>
      <link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/third-appointment/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 00:00:10 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/third-appointment/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday, the 10th, I had my third transcranial magnetic stimulation appointment. Unlike last time, there was no delay; I believe it was because I was the day&amp;rsquo;s first patient. I&amp;rsquo;ll probably be the first again on the next one because it&amp;rsquo;s scheduled for the same hour as yesterday. Even if I&amp;rsquo;m not the first, I&amp;rsquo;ll be one of the first, which means I probably won&amp;rsquo;t have to wait much.
Again, I felt that fantastic relaxation feeling in my body.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Better on the surface</title>
      <link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/better-on-the-surface/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 17:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/better-on-the-surface/</guid>
      <description>I sometimes have a few days when I can walk, mostly normal, and I don&amp;rsquo;t spend the entire day complaining about the pain. It&amp;rsquo;s not that I don&amp;rsquo;t feel pain (I wish it were that!), but that I don&amp;rsquo;t feel as much pain as usual. When people see me on days like these, they always ask me if I&amp;rsquo;m already healed. As soon as I reply &amp;ldquo;No&amp;rdquo;, they look at me like I&amp;rsquo;m lying and trying to trick them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Multiple regions of my body with maximum pain intensity at the same time</title>
      <link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/more-high-intensity-pain-spots/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 05:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/more-high-intensity-pain-spots/</guid>
      <description>By now, I should&amp;rsquo;ve been used to how the pain changes and fluctuates. I am not. I can&amp;rsquo;t get used to having the most hurting part of my body change from one place to the other, causing mixed difficulties as it travels - usually on my upper body. And I can&amp;rsquo;t get used to the changes in intensity, always between high levels.
Since about two weeks ago, I have had one more shit to get used to: having multiple regions of my body with maximum pain intensity at the same time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Farto desta merda</title>
      <link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/farto-desta-merda/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 18:20:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/farto-desta-merda/</guid>
      <description>Alguma vez se sentiram cansados de tudo e sem energia para continuar? Eu tenho-me sentido assim praticamente todos os dias desde há pouco mais de um ano.
Ando sempre cheio de dores, exausto, com o cérebro feito em merda.
Dormir é uma luta, o meu sono está sempre todo fodido: ou não durmo por causa das dores, por causa do stress disto ou, o mais habitual, por causa das duas coisas.
Desde que isto começou, as minhas finanças ficaram viradas do avesso.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To coma or not to coma</title>
      <link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/to-coma-or-not-to-coma/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 23:10:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/to-coma-or-not-to-coma/</guid>
      <description>I can&amp;rsquo;t say I haven&amp;rsquo;t felt desperate due to the constant, unbearable pain and the exhaustion fibromyalgia puts me through. I&amp;rsquo;ve had some days like this, and I&amp;rsquo;ve mentioned it too. I even wrote some of the blog posts here during those periods of diminished mental energy.
I can&amp;rsquo;t also say that, as someone wrote on Reddit, I haven&amp;rsquo;t looked at coma as a way of running away from the pain and the mental fatigue. Or worst escapes, but those desperate thoughts that come forward on the worst times won&amp;rsquo;t be the subject now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Things have gone downhill again</title>
      <link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/downhill-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 18:40:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/downhill-again/</guid>
      <description>For the last few days, the pain intensity has been increasing steadily. I was hoping it was only a fad, and things would stabilize on a somewhat manageable pain level. Again, luck had other plans for me.
Things have been bad, but today tops the last week. I woke up with a crazy ton of pain in my body, and it took me more than one hour to get out of bed - my muscles were (and are) really stiff and soared.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The pain relief didn&#39;t last long</title>
      <link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/pain-increase-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 01:45:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/pain-increase-back/</guid>
      <description>I thought the effects would last longer when I published the previous blog post. I wasn&amp;rsquo;t sure about them enduring a whole week, but at least five days. Not this time; maybe next time. Even so, it lasted longer than last month, so I call it progress, and I keep myself hopeful about this treatment!
Thirty minutes, more or less, after publishing that blog post, I started feeling an increase in the pain intensity. It went from a 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Still feeling the treatment effects</title>
      <link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/second-appointment-less-pain/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 01:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/second-appointment-less-pain/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s already past 1 AM here in Portugal. I was expecting yesterday would be a day with more pain than usual, just like last month, three days after my first transcranial magnetic stimulation appointment.
Pessimistic as it may sound, I believe it&amp;rsquo;s better, in this particular case, to be prepared for the worse in case it happens. If it doesn&amp;rsquo;t, it&amp;rsquo;s a nice and pleasant surprise, don&amp;rsquo;t you agree?
Well, the worst-case scenario didn&amp;rsquo;t come to fruition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Second transcranial magnetic stimulation appointment</title>
      <link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/second-appointment/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 01:20:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/second-appointment/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday I had my second appointment for transcranial magnetic stimulation, a treatment I&amp;rsquo;m undertaking to decrease and manage my pain levels associated with the fibromyalgia I was diagnosed with.
The consultation had a two-hour delay, far from an ideal situation. It&amp;rsquo;s 200kms from my home to the medical centre, so waiting 2 hours, having arrived on time, it&amp;rsquo;s bothersome, to say the least. While I was waiting, I had to shift between sitting and standing up to minimize the increase in the pain level, but in the end, it was worth it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Starting 2022 worst than I ended 2021</title>
      <link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/starting-2022-with-left-foot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 04:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/starting-2022-with-left-foot/</guid>
      <description>Two days after Christmas, I wrote about how painful and tiring the holiday was for me. If you read it, you know that I didn&amp;rsquo;t have much sleep on top of what I just mentioned. I can&amp;rsquo;t say it wasn&amp;rsquo;t expected because it was.
Although a quiet one, the New Year celebration was also expected to be painful and tiring. It was. No surprise here.
After these holidays, I thought I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t get worse than I already was - a few days to recover, and that would be it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Looking back to 2021</title>
      <link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/2021-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 02:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/2021-review/</guid>
      <description>Earth completed another cycle around its star. As it&amp;rsquo;s the tradition in the west, a look back thing needs to be made. This feels like needing to sacrifice an animal to some mythological entity or pray to it; I don&amp;rsquo;t know, it feels weird. As it happens, weird is my first, middle, and last name. Even if I dislike doing it, I&amp;rsquo;ll indulge in this bizarre ritual and make a balance for 2021 from a fibromyalgia standpoint.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No pain, no what!?</title>
      <link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/no-pain-no-go-fuck-yourself/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 04:46:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/no-pain-no-go-fuck-yourself/</guid>
      <description>I just say the above picture posted by u/mordrathe on /r/ChronicPain about that amazingly stupid catchphrase &amp;ldquo;No pain, no gain&amp;rdquo; and it hit home. After spending almost 18 months in constant pain, I gained so much disdain for it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Hellidays were like a beaten to my body</title>
      <link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/hellidays/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2021 04:10:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/hellidays/</guid>
      <description>The Hellidays are gone, and my body is happy with that. Christmas Eve was on a Sunday and Christmas on a Saturday. Then came Sunday, like the third day of the Hellidays. What a fucking beaten it was for me.
On Christmas Eve, I stayed at home during the morning and almost all afternoon. Thank Zeus for that. I couldn&amp;rsquo;t sleep the previous night, only a few hours during the morning. The afternoon was to rest my body and do hot water bottles to ease the pain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My arms hurt as much as my back</title>
      <link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/arms-hurting-like-hell/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Dec 2021 03:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/arms-hurting-like-hell/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday and, so far, today have been crazy and not in a good way. I&amp;rsquo;ve felt pain in my shoulders, arms, hands and wrists since this started, but not so much as now. The intensity is way up there!
It&amp;rsquo;s not just the pain, but the soreness and exhaustion I feel in them too. Yesterday, I even put a hot water bottle in my arms to ease the pain. I&amp;rsquo;ve never done such a thing before!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maybe it&#39;s all bad luck</title>
      <link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/bad_luck/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 02:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/bad_luck/</guid>
      <description>Over the last decade, my health has taken a toll. It wasn&amp;rsquo;t anything serious to the point of getting hospitalized, but severe enough to put me through some hardships I could&amp;rsquo;ve lived without and completely mess my life. I&amp;rsquo;m talking about Irritable Bowel Syndrome (IBS for short).
While not life-threatening, I have a severe form of this syndrome. In most cases, people have light symptoms; I, however, can&amp;rsquo;t go without medication, can&amp;rsquo;t get too stressed and can&amp;rsquo;t eat a lot of stuff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The third day after the first therapy session</title>
      <link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/third-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 03:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/third-day/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday was the third day after the first transcranial neurostimulation session. On the first day, as I wrote before, a tingling sensation started right after the therapy (well, technically, it began during it), and it increased a little as time went by. In over a year, it was the first time that I felt my body relaxing, so it felt terrific.
Unfortunately, the 200km ride back home was tiring. When we got home, I had to go straight to the couch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I had my first transcranial neurostimulation appointment</title>
      <link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/first-transcranial-neurostimulation-appointment/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 01:50:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/first-transcranial-neurostimulation-appointment/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday, the 13th of December, I had my first appointment for transcranial neurostimulation, a promising therapy for dealing - and hopefully fixing - fibromyalgia. I&amp;rsquo;ve written previously about this therapy here and here.
The wife and I drove 200kms to the medical centre, the only one in Portugal with a unit dedicated exclusively to this syndrome, located in Covilhã, a city in the country&amp;rsquo;s interior region. The trip was exhausting; I had to sit for 2 hours and a few minutes, and my body complained a lot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another very, very bad day</title>
      <link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/another-very-very-bad-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Dec 2021 13:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/another-very-very-bad-day/</guid>
      <description>Today is one of those days I don&amp;rsquo;t even get some pain relief by lying down. Well, it started yesterday, when I woke up. I don&amp;rsquo;t know if it was for sleeping too much time in the same position, bad luck, or whatever the fuck it was, but all I know is I woke up in tremendous pain.
My body feels like it&amp;rsquo;s broken and all soared. My arms, legs, lower back, and shoulder blades all hurt a lot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Things I do to &#34;distract&#34; myself from the pain</title>
      <link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/things-i-do-to-distract-myself-from-the-pain/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 02:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/things-i-do-to-distract-myself-from-the-pain/</guid>
      <description>When I&amp;rsquo;m in pain, which is every second of every day, I try to find stuff that helps me distract from it. I can only do most of them when I&amp;rsquo;m not also feeling exhausted, a state that I&amp;rsquo;m frequently in.
If I have the energy, I do at least one of the following:
talk to the wife when she&amp;rsquo;s at home call my parents visit my parents or my in-laws snap some photographs volunteer with Fosshost watch TV listen to some music read online articles play Football Manager Having activities to do is, I believe, very important to keep the mind as sane as possible and avoid going through the rabbit hole of depression.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transcranial magnetic stimulation medical appointment scheduled</title>
      <link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/transcranial-magnetic-stimulation-appointment-scheduled/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 15:20:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/transcranial-magnetic-stimulation-appointment-scheduled/</guid>
      <description>Today, I received a call from the only medical centre in Portugal dedicated to fibromyalgia. They wanted to schedule the first appointment with me.
When I called them to schedule it, they told me they were only registering contacts and that the appointments would only be from January forward. However, today, they scheduled it for next week. I&amp;rsquo;m super excited!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How I keep an increase of pain at bay on family days</title>
      <link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/weekend-hacks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 11:10:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/weekend-hacks/</guid>
      <description>All the doctors I&amp;rsquo;ve seen have told me I need to leave the house and mingle. I hadn&amp;rsquo;t done it much because I&amp;rsquo;m always in pain, and spending a day with the family can be exhausting and painful. I took their advice and every Sunday I try to spend it with my parents or her parents.
Doing it and avoiding the crazy amount of fatigue and pain associated with these days takes some planning. I can&amp;rsquo;t spend all day standing up, but I also can&amp;rsquo;t spend it sitting down on uncomfortable chairs, or I&amp;rsquo;ll be in a lot of pain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Christmas pain song</title>
      <link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/christmas-pain-song/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 05:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/christmas-pain-song/</guid>
      <description>Jingle bell, my back hurts All of my body aches From the tip of the toes All the way to the neck </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>O Christmas tree, O Christmas tree, how painful are your cold days</title>
      <link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/winter-pain/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 23:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/winter-pain/</guid>
      <description>The days keep getting colder and colder, and bearing my pain harder and harder. I write this semi-sitting on the bed, with my back against two pillows, my fingers hurting like crazy, my body hurting even more just for existing. I fucking hate the cold weather!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Study shows that Transcranial Magnetic Stimulation can help decrease the pain</title>
      <link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/transcranial-magnetic-stimulation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 06:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/transcranial-magnetic-stimulation/</guid>
      <description>Two weeks ago, if memory serves me right, I watched the news on TV about a centre dedicated to fibromyalgia opening here I&amp;rsquo;m Portugal. They are performing a study using repetitive transcranial magnetic stimulation (rTMS), which got my attention. I searched for publications about this treatment and got my hands on a 2010 research.
In the study, the authors hypothesize, based on previous works, that dysfunctions in the central nervous system related to changes in central pain processing could be the cause.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another sleepless night</title>
      <link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/pain-insomnia-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 04:40:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/pain-insomnia-2/</guid>
      <description>Again, another night awake with terrible back pain. I have a few of these, but I don&amp;rsquo;t write about them every time they happen: I save this for the worst ones. If I did, I would probably write about this once a week on average.
My legs feel numb and painful too, but not as much as my back. I should probably get a hot water bottle, but I&amp;rsquo;m a bit afraid to walk due to the numbness and pain of the legs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Round and round it goes</title>
      <link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/round-and-round-it-goes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 19:45:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/round-and-round-it-goes/</guid>
      <description>My fibromyalgia most intense pain is like a merry-go-round: everything hurts, but the part of my body that hurts the most keeps changing. One day it&amp;rsquo;s on my lower back, another day is in my shoulder blades, or it&amp;rsquo;s one or both of my legs or my arms.
In the beginning, it was my lower back that hurt the most. It stayed like that for several months. Then, it switched to my shoulder blades. Now it goes around, so it doesn&amp;rsquo;t get bored, I guess.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Things you should not say to someone with chronic pain</title>
      <link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/dont-say-this/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 19:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/dont-say-this/</guid>
      <description>People living with chronic pain often hear things that are beyond irritating and/or demeaning. If we show disappointment or try to explain to people how that&amp;rsquo;s irritating or belittling, we get dismissed. It seems like they think they know more about this than we, the ones who live with it.
If you have a friend, a family member, or anyone in your circle of friends or family living with chronic pain, you should know that there are things you should avoid saying to them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Worst pain level so far</title>
      <link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/worst-pain-so-far/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 03:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/worst-pain-so-far/</guid>
      <description>Since the Fibromyalgia pain started, I&amp;rsquo;ve been forced to classify my days into four categories: good, bad, very bad, and very very bad. The classification depends on the pain I feel and on how disabled I get.
The rarest of them is good. These days are almost as elusive as a neoliberal caring for anything else other than himself.
I had a few of these almost a year ago, in December 2020. The pain was still present, but the level was low, and I could go on with my life without worrying much if an activity or movement would make my body hurt more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Presented myself before a medical board and left the facilities feeling like shit</title>
      <link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/medical-board-made-me-feel-like-shit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 20:20:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/medical-board-made-me-feel-like-shit/</guid>
      <description>Today, I presented myself before Social Security&amp;rsquo;s medical board. I waited almost an hour and didn&amp;rsquo;t wait even more because the other people there saw my suffering and were very kind and asked them to let me cut the line.
I&amp;rsquo;ll continue on paid sick leave. As I was leaving, the &amp;ldquo;doctors&amp;rdquo; in the medical board told me it was a Christmas gift. I&amp;rsquo;m not kidding. Those fuckers mocked me and my disability. I left their facilities feeling like shit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building a good support network is essential</title>
      <link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/support-network/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 01:05:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/support-network/</guid>
      <description>A solid support network of people is of utmost importance for individuals living with chronic pain. During the bad (aka regular) and awful days, having people who can support you and be sympathetic will remove a lot of stress from your shoulders.
They won&amp;rsquo;t fix any issues you experience, but they will help you however they can and be empathetic of your limitations and your illness. This network will act as a pillar to support your crumbling life and avoid it breaking into a messier situation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The impact of chronic pain in memory and concentration</title>
      <link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/chronic-pain-memory-concentration/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 06:32:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/chronic-pain-memory-concentration/</guid>
      <description>In 2007, researchers Dr. Bruce D. Dick and Dr. Saifudin Rashiq, from the University of Alberta&amp;rsquo;s Multidisciplinary Pain Centre in Edmonton, Canada, confirmed chronic pain impairs memory and concentration. Two-thirds of the participants in the research showed significant disruption of attention and memory when tested.
Computerized tests were given to the 24 participants, all of whom had continuous pain lasting for at least six months, to understand the impact of chronic pain on memory. These tests were of working memory and a neuropsychological test of attention.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My experience with Social Security&#39;s medical boards</title>
      <link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/medical-board-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 02:50:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/medical-board-1/</guid>
      <description>Next week, I&amp;rsquo;ll have to present myself before a &amp;ldquo;medical&amp;rdquo; board. This is a standard procedure from Social Security in Portugal to assess if the person has a sickness that prevents them from working. They do this every three months or so while the person is on sick leave.
I won&amp;rsquo;t go into details about the surreal situations I&amp;rsquo;ve experienced with these &amp;ldquo;medical&amp;rdquo; boards, like being shouted at by one of the supposed doctors after another one had made me a question, and I began answering it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How I started cooking after fibromyalgia</title>
      <link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/how-i-cook-and-avoid-increase-in-pain/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 11:37:51 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/how-i-cook-and-avoid-increase-in-pain/</guid>
      <description>When I started feeling the pain caused by fibromyalgia, I was forced to avoid tasks like cleaning the house. I tried to do it before deciding I shouldn&amp;rsquo;t, but it hurt like hell and I couldn&amp;rsquo;t finish It, so I had to let my beautiful wife do this one. Other tasks, however, I was able to keep doing, like cooking, but I had to adapt the way I do them.
And it&amp;rsquo;s about how I adapted the way I do cooking I&amp;rsquo;m writing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I wake up feeling like I ran a marathon</title>
      <link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/energy-depleted/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 10:36:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/energy-depleted/</guid>
      <description>Some of the memories I have from my childhood and teenage years have in common that I never ran out of energy, like the Duracell bunny. During summer, It was usual for my colleagues from my home town and me to play futsal for more than four straight hours. Playing a whole morning and an entire afternoon was also not uncommon, just like going to parties after the matches to get drunk and playing another futsal match the next day wasn&amp;rsquo;t too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A week of waking up around 8h like a fucking clock</title>
      <link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/fucking-clock-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Nov 2021 12:20:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/fucking-clock-1/</guid>
      <description>Today was a good day. I was able to sleep around 4h and woke up at 10h and a couple of minutes, although I would&amp;rsquo;ve loved to sleep 2 or 3 more hours. The downside is that my back hurts more than usual.
Sleeping 6 hours, give or take a couple of minutes, is an improvement compared to the rest of the week, where I always woke up at 8h, 8h30, even if I fell asleep at 5h.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>List of recent fibromyalgia studies</title>
      <link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/list-of-studies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Nov 2021 03:42:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/list-of-studies/</guid>
      <description>I compiled, below, a small list of recent fibromyalgia scientific studies with open access so that people diagnosed with it can better understand the syndrome and find ways to improve symptoms management. Also, people who don&amp;rsquo;t have it can better understand how much patients diagnosed with it suffer.
List Fibromyalgia—A Review for the Psychiatrist
Default mode network changes in fibromyalgia patients are largely dependent on current clinical pain
Metabolic fingerprinting for diagnosis of fibromyalgia and other rheumatologic disorders</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fibromyalgia might be an autoimmune disease</title>
      <link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/fibro-auto-imune-disease-study/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Nov 2021 00:48:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/fibro-auto-imune-disease-study/</guid>
      <description>A recent study points to the hypothesis that fibromyalgia might be an autoimmune disease. The research is being developed by the Institute of Psychiatry, Psychology &amp;amp; Neuroscience at King’s College London, collaborating with the University of Liverpool and the Karolinska Institute.
Fibromyalgia patients suffer from several symptoms, such as pain sensitivity, muscle weakness, increased fatigue, reduced movement, and reduced number of small nerve fibres in the skin. The research is revealing the root of these symptoms is antibodies that increase the activity of pain-sensing nerves throughout the body.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WhY aRe YoU iN pAiN iF yOuR eXaMs ShOw NoThInG wRoNg?</title>
      <link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/why-are-you-in-pain/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 18:22:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/why-are-you-in-pain/</guid>
      <description>Another common complaint I see on /r/fibromyalgia and /r/chronicpain is people asking why someone is in pain if the medical exams show nothing wrong. There is also a variation of the above question: people asking why chronic pain sufferers are in pain if they don&amp;rsquo;t have anything physically wrong.
Those are also annoying. Infuriating, I might add. Again, I won&amp;rsquo;t judge the intention when people ask these questions. However, I can&amp;rsquo;t help but ponder if people think through these questions and their impact before asking them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another sleepless night</title>
      <link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/pain-insomnia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Oct 2021 08:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/pain-insomnia/</guid>
      <description>This night was another sleepless one. Too much pain, even with hot water bottles. With luck, I&amp;rsquo;ll be able to fall asleep for a few hours during the morning or the afternoon. Fingers crossed (not really because they hurt).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I hate cold weather</title>
      <link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/i-hate-cold-weather/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Oct 2021 06:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/i-hate-cold-weather/</guid>
      <description>Cold temperatures arrived in Portugal. With them came an increase in the pain level. What was already bad just became worst.
I was never a big fan of cold, except when I could spend the day in bed, all cosied up. Since fibromyalgia came into my life, it’s different: I can’t spend a whole day laying down because it will make my body hurt even more, and the cold makes the pain even worst.
An average pain level of 6, on a 0 to 10 scale, is now a 7.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HaVe YoU tRiEd (insert random stuff)?</title>
      <link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/have-you-tried/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2021 18:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/have-you-tried/</guid>
      <description>One common complaint I see on /r/fibromyalgia and /r/chronicpain is the questions chronic pain sufferers get asked about if they tried some random stuff, sometimes followed by an &amp;ldquo;it worked for me for my random non-chronic pain. &amp;ldquo;Your all body hurts? Try Yoga&amp;rdquo;.
These questions can be more than annoying. They can be irritating. I won&amp;rsquo;t judge the intention when people ask these questions; I only wonder if they really think people living with chronic pain haven&amp;rsquo;t tried everything they could possibly imagine to relieve the pain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sleep and fibromyalgia</title>
      <link>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/sleep-and-fibro/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fibrohell.github.io/posts/sleep-and-fibro/</guid>
      <description>I’m no stranger to sleepless nights. I suffer from IBS and, on a bad flare, I would go one or two nights without sleeping. This went on and off for a few years until I could finally control this syndrome and get back to my average 9 hours of sleep.
For a few years after getting the IBS under control, I had no trouble sleeping, even when I got the flu. And then came fibromyalgia.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
